Since the fetch weather task is in the fragment, the
由于获取天气的任务是在fragment里面，所以，
menu option to trigger that task should be inside the fragment
启动这个任务的菜单项也应该在fragment里面。
too. That means we should create a new menu layout
也就是说，我们需要建立一个新的菜单布局，
for the fragment and we'll call it forecastfragment.xml. The file will
只是对这个fragment而言，我们叫它forecastfragment.xml。这个文件会被
live within the menu folder under the Resources directory. Inside
保持存放在资源目录里面的menu文件夹里面。在
that file, we'll declare the new menu option for refresh and
这个文件的里面，我们声明了新的菜单项，用来刷新，而且我们赋予
give it this menu item ID. We'll also need to define
它一个菜单项ID。我们同时需要定义一个
a string label for this word, Refresh. We're taking this one
字符标签，来标示“Referesh”。现在，来一步步的操作，
step at a time, so just make the menu xml
先把这个练习中的menu的xml文件
file change in this exercise. If you compile and run
改动一下。如果你编译运行这个app，
the app, there'll be no visible change. It won't show
看起来没有什么变化。它还没有
up on the device yet because we haven't inflated the menu
显示在设备上，是因为，我们还没有从xml里面创建菜单按钮。
item. Inflating it will be in the coding test after
创建部分将在这之后的代码测试部分来做，
this. See how the menu main.xml is implemented as an
请看菜单的main.xml在这个事例中是如何实现的。
example. For an additional hint, see the menu training guide
另外提醒一下，看一下下面的菜单训练指南。
below. When you're done, you can click on this box here.
当你完成的时候，你可以在这里单击这个按钮